

# LE PHU CUONG

WEB DEVELOPER

**DATE OF BIRTH** 

June 21, 2000

**EMAIL** 

lpcuong2106@gmail.com

**GENDER** 

Male

**ADDRESS** 

Long Xuyen, An Giang

**PHONE** 

0349265776

**WEBSITE** 

https://fb.com/lpcuong2106

#### INTRODUCTION

Hello, you can call me Kaito, I am a senior student at Can Tho University, majoring in Software Engineering and I will graduate in the last year 2022. I have 2 years of experience in working as a frontend web developer at ViecCo and 1 year as a Full-stack developer at AxonActive software company. Besides, I am a Software Engineer. I was passionate about code, I was self-study to learn everything related to code through online courses and especially I am really interested in the work as a front-end developer, I have been involved in many practical projects related to Web development.

# CAN THO UNIVERSITY

Major: Software engineering

GPA: 3.79/4

**EDUCATION** 

Aug 2018 → Dec2021

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### AXONACTIVE SOFTWARE COMPANY

Feb 2021 → Present

#### Full-Stack developer

I am working for Full Stack developer position at AxonActive. We build a lot of microservices for websites about social insurance, fintech, etc in Switzerland.



#### VIEC.CO SOFTWARE COMPANY

Feb 2020 → 2021

#### Remote Front End developer

I am working for Front End developer position at ViecCo in Website and Mobile for fields related to applying many jobs for the employer to help their having income for your life.



#### COFFEEMUG SOFTWARE COMPANY

May 2019 → July2019

#### Internship PHP developer

I have been interned at Coffeemug.com

#### MY PROJECT



### HIRING JOB

Jun 2021 → Oct 2021

#### Node JS

Technical: Laravel API. React Js

Description: A essay project about managing and hiring for companies. This website will help the person who wanna find a good job or find a good

### **SKILLS**

HTML/CSS (SCSS)/JS

React Js

Java/Java Spring

Node Js/ Express Js

Laravel

MySQL MonggoDB GraphQL React Native Cloud Service (GCP, Firebase, GG studio,...) Manage Server (Linux) - Deploy to server (Nginx, Jenkin,...) ulletPhotoshop English

#### REFERENCES

Github: github.com/phucuongit Linkedin: linkedin.com/in/lpcuong2

CV online: cv.sharenows.com (deprecated)

company. This one will provide the workers to companies.

Demo: https://ccv.sharenows.com

- Admin Account: nfq@gmail.com/08081508

## MANAGE AND INJECT COVID VACCINATION Jun 2021 → Oct 2021

#### Node JS

Technical: Laravel API, Vue Js

**Description**: A project about managing and injecting covid vaccination for citizens. An admin system can manage amount of vaccination, type of vaccine, citizens,...

**Demo**: https://covid-nienluan.sharenows.com/admin (deprecated)

- Admin Account: nienluan/123123

### JOB CRAWLER

Dec 2020 → Feb 2021

#### Node JS

**Technical**: Node Js, TS, GCP(BigQuery, GG studio, firebase - Firestore), AWS (EC2)

**Description**: A project about crawling many job page such as timviecnhanh, vieclam24h, careerbuilder, so on and upload this data to BigQuery

**Demo**: Private

# **STUDENT MANAGEMENT SYSTEM - REGISTER** Aug 2020 → Dec 2020 **SUBJECT**

#### Java Spring

Technical: Java Spring

**Description**: A project about student managing system. People can register subject and teacher can mark the score for student.

Demo: https://htql.sharenows.com (deprecated)

- Admin Account: cuongle/12345678- Student Account: hs1/12345678- Teacher Account: gv1/12345678

## **ECOMMERCE STORE**

Aug 2020 → Dec 2020

#### PHP

Technical: PHP native

**Description**: A project about e-commerce store

Demo: https://b1805744.000webhostapp.com/b1805744/khachhang

(deprecated)

# TELEGRAM BOT - SYSTEM RECORD THE SCORE Aug 2020 → Sep 2020 FOR EMPLOYEE

#### Node JS

Technical: NodeJs, MongoDb

**Description**: A project about recording the score between staff. Staff can give and claim score when they do something or help other people

**Demo**: https://t.me/employer\_recognition\_bot

# TOOL AUTO REGISTER SUBJECT CAN THO UNIVERSITY

Aug 2019 → Sep 2019

#### React JS

Technical: React JS, Chrome Extension

**Description**: A tool support for registering subjects in Can Tho University. You can schedule your study plan and the tool will auto-register following you plan

**Demo**: https://www.youtube.com/watch? v=YCdCd3ThCkU&ab\_channel=LEPHUCUONG

### **CERTIFICATIONS**

Certification at Codelearn, Hackerank. I have learnt many things at here:

2018 - 2020

- https://codelearn.io/profile/173289
- https://www.hackerrank.com/lpcuong2106